

IBRAHIM HOSSAIN

EXPERT ON
Front-End Web Developer

CONTACT ME

- **S** +88 01307 874 605
- □ ibrahimhossain526@gmail.com
- Nuril Chowrasta, Vatara, Dhaka 1229

MY PORTFOLIO

https://protfolio-ibrahim.netlify.app/

SKILLS TOOLS

Photopea

HTML & CSS

BootStrap

JavaScript

React Js

Next Js

Swiper js

Node js

Express js

Mongo DB

Mongoose

MS Office

Camtasia

Figma

PROFILE

Hi everyone.

This is Ibrahim

Skilled Front-End Web Developer with 3 years of experience in HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, React JS, Next JS, Swiper JS, and other JavaScript libraries. Seeking opportunities to contribute to innovative web development projects.

WORK EXPERIENCE

SOFT IT CARE

Front-End Web Developer [2022-2023]



• My task in this company was to produce many Landing pages, Multiple web page variety of digital products The First Ever Automated ECommerce Sales Funnel. I should meet their style and vision while accomplishing the tasks. I also collaborated with various internal and external teams to discuss the goals and target audiences.

MAINUL EXTENSION

Digital Marketing Experts [2021-2022]

• Ecommerce support for FB Marketplace

TEH TARIK PLACE

supervisor

• (Other side job) Teh Tarik Place is a popular Malaysian restaurant chain that specializes in traditional Malaysian cuisine

EDUCATION

• BACHELOR OF BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION (BBA)

Dhaka Commerce College

HSC

Science

Govt. Mostafabia Kamil Madrasha [2014] Result GPA - 4.17 out of 5.00

DHAKIL(SSC)

Science

Boailmari kamil madrasha [2012] Result GPA - 5.00 out of 5.00

EXTRA KNOWLEDGE

Digital Marketing Facebook Ads Search engine optimization-SEO Facebook Marketplace Google Map keyword research

PERSINAL INFO

Father's Name : Md. Abdul Mozid
Mother's Name : Nazma khatun
Date of Birth : 12/03/1996
Nationality : Bangladeshi
Religion : Islam (Sunni)
Marital Status : Unmarried.
Height : 6 Feet
Weight : 78 kg
Blood Group : B+

Permanent Address

Village: Purbovabanipur

P/O: Santhia P.S: Santhia District : Pabna

Present Address

Khan Villah, Ka-60, Jowar Sahara Bazar Road, Kuril Chowrasta, Vatara, Dhaka 1229

TRAINING

COMPUTER APPLICATION

Net Pass Computer Training center [Jan-Jun, 2012] Result Result 5.00

• FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPMENT Online Courses and YouTube [2020-2021]

SOFT IT CARE

Inturn [2020-2021] Front-End Web Developer

REFERENCE

Abu Musa

Digital marketing oraimo Bangladesh Contact: 01744690616